Finding Aid for the C. Rick Chappell Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
C. Rick Chappell Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0701
23.82 linear feet
- Nobel Symposia, March 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Nobel Symposia, March 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Space Lab 3 CNN Commentary, April-May 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Space Lab 3 CNN Commentary, April 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Space Lab 3 CNN Commentary –Promotional Booklet, April 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Space Lab 3 CNN Commentary, April 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Space Lab 3 Press Materials, April 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Space Lab 3 Press Materials, July 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- NASA Awards and ABC News Close-up, March-September 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ATLAS Mission Water Survival Training Materials, May 1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Big Talks –“Council on Graduate Schools” by P. Syverson and Moira J. Maguire, March 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Big Talks –Apollo 11 Anniversary by President George W. Bush, 1989 and Budget of the United States, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Big Talks –Articles on Space Race, 1958-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Heavens and the Earth: a Political History of the Space Age. Walter McDougall -Notes (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Heavens and the Earth: a Political History of the Space Age. Walter McDougall - Photocopies (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Big Talks –Notes and Clippings, September 1987-September 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Big Talks “What Future for the United States in Space” NASA, September 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Big Talks Articles on Space Exploration, November 1958-September 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Space Science Heritage Photographs, December 1990-October 1993 (7) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- NASA Headquarters/Washington, March-April 1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- NASA Headquarters/Washington, April 1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- NASA Headquarters/Washington, March-May 1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- NASA Headquarters/Washington, May 1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- NASA Headquarters/Washington, February-May 1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- NASA Headquarters/Washington, February 1991 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- David Reasoner Tribute Materials, May-June 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- David Reasoner Tribute Slides, April 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Aerospace Education, December 1995-March 1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Aerospace Education, December 1995-February 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Aerospace Education, December 1995-February 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Aerospace Education, October-December 1995 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, August 1992-November 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, February 1991-March 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, March 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, September-November 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July-October 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Ground Truth Studies, April-September 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, March-April 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, January 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July 1990-January 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, January-July 1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Ground Truth Studies Teachers’ Handbook, June 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, January 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, May-June 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July-August 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Summer Sessions, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, May-July 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, April 1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, April 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, April-June 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, March-May 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, September 1990-September 1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, September 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, November1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July-August 1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July-August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July-September 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Aspen Global Change Institute -Publicity, September 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July-August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July-August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Publicity, July-August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July-August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July-August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, April-July 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, March-August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, August 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Aspen Global Change Institute/International Space year(ISY) Connection, June-July 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, June-July 1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, December 1989-April 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Windstar Foundation Grant, December 1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Ground Truth Studies, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Ground Truth Studies, March 1992-June 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Ground Truth Studies Teachers’ Handbook, March 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Ground Truth Studies, February 1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Ground Truth Studies, December 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Aspen Global Change Institute –Education Plan/Ground Truth Studies, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
- International Space year (ISY) –Training in Remote Sensing, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Association of Space Explorers, 1989-July 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- International Space Station (ISS) Investigator Workshop, July-August 1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- International Space Station (ISS) Investigator Workshop, July-August 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Space Station Science Operations, August 1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Space Station Science Operations, August 1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Space Station Science Operations, August 1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Space Station Science Operations, August 1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Space Station Science Operations, July-August 1996 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, January-February 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, December 1993-January 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, December 1993-January 1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, November 1993-January 1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, August-December 1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, August-November 1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, May-July 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, June-July 1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, April-June 1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, March-April 1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial -Photographs, March1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, March 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, March-September 1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial –NASA Alumni League Support, March-September 1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, December 1992-March 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, August-October 1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, August 1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial -Photographs, July 1992-January 1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Marshall Space Flight Center Employee Living Memorial, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Global Learning and Observations to Benefit the Environment (GLOBE)–Teachers’ Guide, April 1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Global Learning and Observations to Benefit the Environment (GLOBE)–Implementation Plan (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Global Learning and Observations to Benefit the Environment (GLOBE) -Materials (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Global Learning and Observations to Benefit the Environment (GLOBE)–Talks with Jack Dailey, December 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Global Learning and Observations to Benefit the Environment (GLOBE) –Materials, June 1994-March 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Global Learning and Observations to Benefit the Environment (GLOBE) –Appointment, June 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Global Learning and Observations to Benefit the Environment (GLOBE) –Press Announcement and Job Duties, May 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- USA Inc., November 1993-February 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- USA Inc., May-October 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- USA Inc., February-September 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- USA Inc., August 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- USA Inc., March –May 1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- USA Inc. –Technology In Action/Marshall Space Flight Center –Annual Report, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- USA Inc., November 1990-April 1991 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- USA Inc. –Photographs (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Marshall Space Flight Center -Technology Utilization Presentation, January 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- NASA Technology Transfer Report of Technology Transfer Team, December 1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- NASA –Career, July 1989-June 1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- NASA –Career, March 1989-August 1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- NASA –Career, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- NASA –Career –Associate Director Promotion at Marshall Space Flight Center, October 1987-February 1988 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- NASA –Career Awards and Recognition/Promotion, October 1987-October 1989 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- NASA –Career –Associate Director Promotion at Marshall Space Flight Center, October 1987 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- NASA –Career Awards and Recognition –Spacelab, December 1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- NASA –Career Awards and Recognition, April 1981-August 1983 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- NASA –Career, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- NASA –Spacelab Mission One –Program Review, January 18, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- NASA –Investigators Working Group (Box 6, Folder 2)
- NASA –Investigators Working Group (Box 6, Folder 3)
- NASA –Atmospheric, Magnetospheric and Plasmas in Space(AMPS)–Payload Technical Summary, December 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- NASA –Final Report of the Science Definition Panel for Atmospheric, Magnetosphere and Plasmas in Space(AMPS) Spacelab Payload, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- NASA –TRW AMPS Payload Design, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- NASA –Technical Summary, May 1976 –AMPS Spacelab Payload Definition Report (Box 6, Folder 7)
- NASA –AMPS Project Requirements Document –Draft, January 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- NASA –Scientific Objectives for Atmospheric Physics from AMPS –Appendix 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- NASA –Baseline AMPS Instrument Functional Requirements, February 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection Group (Box 7, Folder 1)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection Group (Box 7, Folder 2)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection Group (Box 7, Folder 3)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection (Box 7, Folder 4)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection (Box 7, Folder 5)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection (Box 7, Folder 6)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection (Box 7, Folder 7)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection (Box 7, Folder 8)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection (Box 7, Folder 9)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection (Box 7, Folder 10)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection (Box 7, Folder 11)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection (Box 7, Folder 12)
- NASA –Payload Specialist Selection (Box 7, Folder 13)
- NASA –Investigator Working Group (Box 7, Folder 14)
- NASA –Investigator Working Group (Box 7, Folder 15)
- NASA –Investigator Working Group (Box 7, Folder 16)
- NASA –Investigator Working Group (Box 7, Folder 17)
- NASA –Investigator Working Group (Box 7, Folder 18)
- NASA –Creating the Spacelab (Box 8, Folder 1)
- NASA –Creating the Spacelab (Box 8, Folder 2)
- NASA –Creating the Spacelab (Box 8, Folder 3)
- NASA –Creating the Spacelab (Box 8, Folder 4)
- NASA –Performance Evaluation–Rick Chappell (Box 8, Folder 5)
- NASA –Performance Evaluation–Rick Chappell (Box 8, Folder 6)
- NASA –Performance Evaluation–Rick Chappell (Box 8, Folder 7)
- NASA –Performance Evaluation–Rick Chappell (Box 8, Folder 8)
- NASA –Performance Evaluation–Rick Chappell (Box 8, Folder 9)
- NASA –Biographical Information and Photographs (Box 8, Folder 10)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, March 1993-February 1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, January –June 1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, September-December 1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, July-September 1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, September 1991-August 1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, January –June 1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, February 1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, November 1991-January 1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, July-November 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, August –October 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- NASA –Autograph Requests, February –May 1991 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- School Visits –Thank Yous, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- School Visits –Thank Yous, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- School Visits –Thank Yous, April 1993 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- School Visits –Thank Yous, January –April 1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- School Visits –Thank Yous, January –April 1993 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- School Visits –Thank Yous, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- School Visits –Thank Yous, February 1988-February 1989 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Speaking Events –Educational, March –May 1993 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Speaking Events –Educational, December 1992 –November 1993 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Speaking Events –Thank Yous, December 1990 –June 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Speaking Events –Thank Yous, November 1990 –March 1991 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Speaking Events –Thank Yous, June 1990 –March 1991 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Speaking Events –Thank Yous, November 1981 –March 1984 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Speaking Events –Thank Yous, September 1975 –August 1981 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- I.E.E.E.E. Globecom –Thank Yous, March 1989 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- NASA –ATLAS 1 Mission –Thank Yous, April 1992 –February 1994 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- NASA –Spacelab 1 –Thank Yous, December 1981 –June 1984 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- NASA –Educational Visits –Thank Yous, June 1991 –July 1992 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- NASA –Educational Visits –Thank Yous, June 1991 –April 1992 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- NASA –Educational Visits –Thank Yous, April –June 1990 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- NASA –Educational Visits –Thank Yous, March –June 1990 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- NASA –Educational Visits –Thank Yous, April –June 1989 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- NASA –Educational Visits –Thank Yous, June –July 1989 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- NASA –Educational Visits –Thank Yous, May –November 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- NASA –Educational Visits –Thank Yous, April 1979 –January 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- NASA –Thank Yous, November 1989 –September 1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- NASA –Thank Yous, May 1991 –June 1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- NASA –Thank Yous, February –June 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- NASA –Thank Yous, February –May 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- NASA –Thank Yous, April –November 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- NASA –Thank Yous, December 1985 –November 1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- NASA –Thank Yous, September 1984 –November 1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- NASA –Career, June 1996 –August 1997 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Intergovernmental Personnel Act (IPA) –Vanderbilt University, August 1995 –July 1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Intergovernmental Personnel Act (IPA) –Vanderbilt University, July 1992 –August 1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- First Amendment Center, August 1996 –March 1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Worlds Apart: How the Distance Between Science and Journalism Threatens America’s Future –Book Requests, June 1999 –November 2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Worlds Apart: How the Distance Between Science and Journalism Threatens America’s Future –Book Requests, April –July 1998 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Worlds Apart: How the Distance Between Science and Journalism Threatens America’s Future –Book Requests, April 1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Worlds Apart: How the Distance Between Science and Journalism Threatens America’s Future –Book Requests, July –December 1998 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Worlds Apart: How the Distance Between Science and Journalism Threatens America’s Future C-Span Talk (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Worlds Apart: How the Distance Between Science and Journalism Threatens America’s Future -Publicity (Box 10, Folder 19)
- National Public Radio (NPR) Science Friday –Talk and Exchange Club Jacksonville, Florida Talk, September 1997 –May 1999 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- National Public Radio (NPR) On the Media –Talks, December 1996 –July 1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- “Freedom Speaks” Series, January –April 1997 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Vanderbilt –Nashville Forum, May 1997 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Minority Writers Seminar, May 1997 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Career Opportunities Committee, December 1996 –March 1997 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Career Opportunities Committee, April –August 1997 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Student Career Center Seminar, September –October 1997 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Freedom Forum Center, October –December 1997 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Council of Scientific Society Presidents –Meeting, May 1998 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Communicating Science Conference –Hamilton College, October 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Oak Ridge National Laboratory and Woods Hole –Visits, October –November 1998 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Science Communication Working Group, October –November 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Eastern Analytical Symposium, November 1998 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Chroniclers of Discovery Career Symposium, September 1998 –February 1999 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Chroniclers of Discovery Career Symposium, February –April 1999 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Chroniclers of Discovery Career Symposium, March –April 1999 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Chroniclers of Discovery Career Symposium, March –April 1999 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Chroniclers of Discovery Career Symposium, February –March 1999 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Chroniclers of Discovery Career Symposium, January –March 1999 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Chroniclers of Discovery Career Symposium, April 1999 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Chroniclers of Discovery Career Symposium, March 1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Chronicle of Higher Education –Article by Rick Chappell “The Challenge of Communicating Science to the Public” 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Hearing on Communicating Science and Engineering in a Sound Bite World – Testimony, May 14, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Hearing on Communicating Science and Engineering in a Sound Bite World – Testimony, May 14, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Hearing on Communicating Science and Engineering in a Sound Bite World – Testimony, May 14, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Hearing on Communicating Science and Engineering in a Sound Bite World – Testimony, May 14, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Hearing on Communicating Science and Engineering in a Sound Bite World – Testimony –Notes (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Reporting of Space, Science and Technology in America –Presentation to Joe B. Wyatt, January 9, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Communicating Science and Engineering –Meeting with Chancellor Jow B. Wyatt, May 13, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Coupling, Energetics and Dynamics of the Atmospheric Regions (CEDAR) – Lecture, June 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Coupling, Energetics and Dynamics of the Atmospheric Regions (CEDAR) – Lecture, June 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Harry D. Powell Observatory Naming Ceremony –East Tennessee State University, September 1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- First Amendment Center –Vanderbilt School of Engineering, June 1996 –June 2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- First Amendment Center –Vanderbilt School of Engineering, December 1997 –; January 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- World Congress of Science Producers –Science and the Media Panel (WGBH), November –December 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- World Congress of Science Producers –Science and the Media Panel (WGBH), November –December 1998 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Jet Propulsion Lab/Cal Tech Management Association Workshop, October –; December 1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Council for Chemical Research, September 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Department of Energy Low Dose Radiation Research Program, November 1999 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Board on Earth Sciences and Resources, October –November 1999 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Montgomery Bell Academy –Talk, November 1999 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Research! America –Albuquerque, New Mexico, December 1999 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Minnesota Educational Effectiveness Program (MEEP) –Spring Leadership Conference, April 1999 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Minnesota Educational Effectiveness Program (MEEP) –Spring Leadership Conference, April 1999 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Society of Toxicology –Annual Meeting, September 1998 –April 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Science Now! Science and the Media Seminar –Melbourne, Australia, December 1998 –May 1999 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Science Now! Science and the Media Seminar –Melbourne, Australia, February –; April 1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Science Now! Science and the Media Seminar –Melbourne, Australia, February –; May 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Science Now! Science and the Media Seminar –Melbourne, Australia, May 1999 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Science Now! Science and the Media Seminar –Melbourne, Australia, May 1999 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- American Association for the Advancement of Sciences (AAAS) and National Association of Science Writers (NASW) Conferences, February 16-18, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, December 1998 –October 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, May –August 2000 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, June –August 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, July –August 2000 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, March –July 2000 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, January –April 2000 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, January –February 2000 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Aspen Global Change Institute, February –March 2001 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- American Meteorological Society –Meeting, January 2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- American Meteorological Society –Meeting, January 2002 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- American Meteorological Society –Meeting, September 2001 –January 2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- American Meteorological Society –Meeting, February 2001 –January 2002 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- American Meteorological Society –Meeting, January 2001 –January 2002 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- American Meteorological Society –Meeting, January 2001 –January 2002 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- American Meteorological Society –Meeting, November 2000 –January 2001 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- American Meteorological Society –Meeting, August –November 2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)